Guide to the Peter Salovey, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Peter Salovey, President of Yale University, Records
2012-2018
RU 1157
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
31
(31 boxes)
The records consist of subject files, correspondence, annual reports, and memoranda documenting Peters Salovey's activities as president of Yale University. The records contain substantive documentation on virtually every aspect of the university administration, schools, departments, and other major units.
Yale University. President's Office
General
Forms part of Yale Record Group 2-A (YRG 2-A), Records of the Yale president's office.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collection is restricted until the end of Peter Salovey's tenure as president of Yale University.
Biographical / Historical
Peter Salovey is the twenty-third president of Yale University and the Chris Argyris Professor of Psychology.
He holds secondary faculty appointments in the School of Management, the School of Public Health, the Institution for Social and Policy Studies, and the Sociology Department. He became president of the university in July 2013.
President Salovey has led the development of new programs and facilities across the schools and departments of Yale, including restructuring the leadership of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences and opening two new residential colleges, expanding Yale College by 15 percent. He is advancing innovative teaching on campus; amplifying Yale's partnerships in Africa, Asia, and other parts of the world; and enhancing interdisciplinary collaboration and entrepreneurial opportunity for faculty and students. President Salovey is committed to increasing access to a Yale education for students worldwide regardless of their financial background.
Prior to becoming president, President Salovey served as the provost of Yale University from 2008 to 2013. As provost, he facilitated strategic planning and initiatives such as enhancing career development and mentoring opportunities for all Yale faculty members; promoting faculty diversity; creating the Office of Academic Integrity; establishing the University-wide Committee on Sexual Misconduct; developing the West Campus; and overseeing the university's budget during the global financial crisis.
Other leadership roles at Yale have included serving as chair of the Department of Psychology (2000 to 2003); dean of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (2003 to 2004); and dean of Yale College (2004 to 2008).
After receiving an A.B. (psychology) and A.M. (sociology) from Stanford University in 1980 with departmental honors and university distinction, President Salovey earned three degrees at Yale in psychology: M.S. (1983), M.Phil. (1984), and Ph.D. (1986). Since joining the Yale faculty in 1986, he has studied the connections among emotion, health communication, and health behavior, with a special focus on emotional intelligence. He played key roles in multiple Yale programs including the Health, Emotion, and Behavior Laboratory, which President Salovey founded and is now the Center for Emotional Intelligence; the Center for Interdisciplinary Research on AIDS; and the Cancer Prevention and Control Research Program.
President Salovey has authored or edited over a dozen books translated into eleven languages and published hundreds of journal articles and essays. With John D. Mayer, he developed a broad framework called "Emotional Intelligence," the theory that just as people have a wide range of intellectual abilities, they also have a wide range of measurable emotional skills that profoundly affect their thinking and action.
In addition to teaching and mentoring scores of graduate students, President Salovey has won both the William Clyde DeVane Medal for Distinguished Scholarship and Teaching in Yale College and the Lex Hixon '63 Prize for Teaching Excellence in the Social Sciences. He has received honorary degrees from the University of Pretoria (2009), Shanghai Jiao Tong University (2014), National Tsing Hua University (2014), and Harvard University (2015). In 2013, he was elected to the American Academy of Arts and Sciences and to the National Academy of Medicine.
President Salovey and his wife, Marta Elisa Moret, have lived in New Haven since they arrived as graduate students more than thirty years ago. Ms. Moret, a 1984 graduate of the Yale School of Public Health, is the president of Urban Policy Strategies, LLC, which provides program evaluation and technical assistance to community-based health organizations. Ms. Moret is also active with the Association of Yale Alumni and has served on its board of governors. She previously held positions in the Edward Zigler Center in Child Development and Social Policy, the Community Foundation for Greater New Haven, and the Hispanic Health Council. Ms. Moret was the deputy commissioner for the Connecticut Department of Social Services from 1991 to 1994.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject files, correspondence, annual reports, and memoranda documenting Peter Salovey's activities as president of Yale University. The records contain substantive documentation on virtually every aspect of the university administration, schools, departments, and other major units.
Arrangement
The material is arranged as received from the creator of the records.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; College presidents; Educators
- Records of the president, 2012-2018; Accession 2019-A-0015
  - Academic Files
    - Department of African American Studies Chair, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Studies Meeting Notes, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Department of Anthropology Chair Appointment Bribiescas, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Department of Anthropology Professor MacCurdy Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Department of Applied Physics Meeting Notes, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Department of Applied Physics Merger-Report and Correspondence, 2011-2014 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Department of Applied Physics Devoret Meeting Notes, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Department of Applied Physics Quantum Institute Proposal, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - School of Architecture Accreditation, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - School of Architecture Dean Search, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - School of Architecture Dean's Council Conversation with President Salovey, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - School of Architecture Goals and Priorities, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - School of Architecture Jim Vlock Building Project Talking Points, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - School of Art Dean Messer Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - School of Art Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Department of Astronomy Chair Appointment Van Dokkum, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Department of Astronomy Van Dokkum Notes, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Department of Biomedical Engineering Strategic Plan, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Department of Chemical Engineering Chair Appointment Van Tassel, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Department of Chemical Engineering Elimelech Correspondence, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Department of Comparative Literature Chair Appointment Quint, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Department of Comparative Literature Quint Meeting Notes, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Department of Computer Science Chair Appointment Feigenbaum, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Department of Computer Science Chair interviews, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Dean's Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Directed Studies Kronman Meeting Notes, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - School of Drama Binger Center for New Theater Report, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - School of Drama Dean Bundy Meeting Notes, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - School of Drama Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - School of Drama Reperatory Theatre Correspondence, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Department of East Asian Languages and Literatures Chair Appointment Lu, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Department of Ecology and Evolutionary Biology Chair Appointment Turner, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Department of Ecology and Evolutionary Biology Chair Interviews, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Department of Economics Candidate Tamer, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Department of Economics Chair Appointment Bergemann, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Department of Electrical Engineering Chair Appointment Chair Appointment Han, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - School of Engineering Dean's Leadership Council Meeting, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences Annual Report, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - School of Engineering and Applied Science Complaint, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - School of Engineering and Applied Science Defense Science Study Group Corresp., 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - School of Engineering and Applied Science Discussion of Situation, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - School of Engineering and Applied Science Engineering and Science Weekend, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - School of Engineering and Applied Science Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences Leadership Council Meeting, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences Saltzman Notes, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Department of English Chair Appointment Hammer, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Department of English Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Faculty Dinner with President Elect Salovey and Marry Miller Notes, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Faculty Leave Guidelines, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Academic Review Committee Report, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Case Summary, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Chairs, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Chairs Breakfasts, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Chairs List, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Chairs Meetings, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Committee Appointments, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Dean Appointment Gendler, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Dean Gendler Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Dean Planning, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Decanal Structure Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Divisional Director Roles, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences External Advisory Board for Diversity, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Faculty Senate Committee, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Faculty Slots, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences New Faculty Biographies, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Reorganization, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Senate Implementation Committee Report, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Senate Planning Committee, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Senate Proposal Summary Sheet, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Senate Slot Book, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Senate Slot Books, 2011-2013 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Senate Steering Meeting, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Senate Steering Meeting, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Film and Media Studies Meeting Notes, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Film and Media Studies Morris Documentary Discand Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies History Booklet, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies Leadership Council Dean Cramer Corresp., 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies Yale Myers Forest Proposal, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Department of French Chair Bloch Article, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Department of German Language and Literature Chair Appointment Campe, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Dean Appointment Cooley, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Matriculation Ceremony Pamphlet, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Matriculation Ceremony Pamphlet, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Department of History Pitti Notes, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Department of History Tooze, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Humanities Initiative Bloch Meeting Notes, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Humanities Program Chair Appointment Bloch, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Humanities Program Appointment Garsten Announcement, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Humanities Program Chair Bloch Proposal and Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Humanities Program Concerns Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Humanities Program Garsten Meeting Notes, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - International Security Studies Professor Kennedy Book Proposal, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Department of Italian Language and Literature Chair Appointment Mazzotta, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Judaic Studies Chair Fraade Meeting, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Judaic Studies Chair Appointment Fraade Announcement, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Judaic Studies Program Activities, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Department of Italian Languages Literatures Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Latin American and Iberian Studies Programmatic Events, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Law School Complaint, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Law School Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Law School Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Law School Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Law School Dean Post Review, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Law School Dean Reappointment Post, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Law School Global Constitutionalism Dinner, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Law School Global Constitutionalism Seminar Photographs and Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Law School Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Law School Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Law School Kronman Meeting Notes, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Law School Linman Newsletter and Correspondence, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Law School middle East Legal Studies Seminar Correspondence, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Law School Native American Emrollment, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Department of Linguistics Chair Appointment Frank, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Department of Linguistics Concerns Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Macroeconomics Proposal, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - School of Management Asian Institute of Management memo of understanding, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - School of Management Board of Advisors Meeting, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 123)
    - School of Management Buisiness and Society Panel Program and Notes, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 124)
    - School of Management Charles Butt Proposal, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 125)
    - School of Management China Leadership Center, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 126)
    - School of Management Goals and Priorities, 2012-2014 (Box 1, Folder 127)
    - School of Management New Benefit Charges Appeal, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 128)
    - School of Management Opening Ceremony, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 129)
    - School of Management Reunion, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 130)
    - School of Management Salovey Presentation, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 131)
    - School of Management Site Photographs, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 132)
    - School of Management Seoul National University Memorandum of Understanding, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 133)
    - School of Management Technologico De Monterrey and Egade Business School MOU, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 134)
    - Department of Mathematics Chair Appointment Jones Announcement, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 135)
    - Department of Mathematics Chair Appointment Minsky, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 136)
    - Department of Mathematics Chair Minsky Notes, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 137)
    - Department of Mathematics Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 138)
    - School of Medicine Ad Hoc Task Force on Gender Equity Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 139)
    - School of Medicine Dean Appointment Alpern, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 140)
    - School of Medicine Dean Search Committee, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - School of Medicine Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - School of Medicine Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - School of Medicine Issues, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - School of Medicine Lafell Notes, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - School of Medicine Lifton Notes, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - School of Medicine Carolyn Mazure Dinner, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - School of Medicine Medical School Women, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - School of Medicine Program for Humanities in Medicine, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - School of Medicine Sabatini, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - School of Medicine Yale Scholars Program, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - School of Medicine Yale New Haven Hospital Healthcare Implications, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Middle Eastern Studies Turkish and Persian Correspondence, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Department of Molecular, Cellular, and Developmental Biology Chair Appoint Breaker, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Department of Molecular, Cellular, and Developmental Biology Notes, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Department of Molecular, Cellular, and Developmental Biology Pollard Notes, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - School of Music Alumni Brochure, 2008-2013 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - School of Music Chair Appointment Hepokowski, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - School of Music Conversation with Salovey and John Adams, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - School of Music Convocation Invitation, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - School of Music Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - School of Music Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - School of Music Goals and Priorities, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - School of Music Hepokowski Notes, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - School of Music Washington Speaks Premiere, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Department of Near Eastern Languages and Civilizations Acting Chair Appoint Kraus, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Department of Near Eastern Languages and Civilizations Talking Points, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - New Faculty Member Orientation, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - New Faculty Reception Invitation, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - New Faculty Reception Invitations, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - School of Nursing Annual Report, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - School of Nursing Annual Report, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - School of Nursing Building Dedication, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - School of Nursing Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - School of Nursing Dean Grey, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - School of Nursing Dean Search, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - School of Nursing Dean Search Report Folder 1 of 2, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - School of Nursing Dean Search Report Folder 2 of 2, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - School of Nursing Dean Search Doctor of Nursing Practice Program CCNE Site Visit, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - School of Nursing Doctorate Self-Study Program, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - School of Nursing Gift Opportunities, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - School of Nursing Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Department of Philosophy Chair Appointment Darwall, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Department of Philosophy Chair Appointment Gendler, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Department of Physics Chair Appointment Chair Appointment Tipton, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Department of Physics Devoret's Birthday Symposium, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Department of Political Science Chair Appointment Wilkinson, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Department of Political Science Chair Inteview, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Department of Political Science Meeting Notes, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Department of Psychology Chair Appointment Keil, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Department of Psychology Meeting Notes, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Department of Psychology Resumes, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - School of Public Health Capello Notes, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - School of Public Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - School of Public Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Department of Religious Studies Chair Appointment Hayes, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Department of Slavic Languages and Literatures Chair Appointment Alexandrov, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Department of Slavic Languages and Literatures Chair Appointment Goldblatt, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Division of Social Sciences Director Appointment Adams, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Division of Social Sciences Dovidio Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Department of Sociology Anderson Meeting Notes, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Department of Sociology Chair Appointment Breen, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Department of Spanish and Portuguese Chair Adorno, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Department of Spanish and Portuguese Human Resources Issue, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Yale College Announcement, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Yale College Board of Permanent Officers and Graduate School Joint Meeting, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Yale College Dean Appointment Holloway, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Yale College Dean Holloway Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Yale College Dean Miller, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Yale College Dean Miller Notes, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Yale College Deam Miller Reception, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Yale College Dean's Office Whobrey Announcement, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Yale College Expansion and Admissions, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Yale College Faculty Meeting, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Yale College Faculty Meeting, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Yale College Faculty Meeting, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Yale College Faculty Meeting, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Yale College Faculty Meeting, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Yale College Faculty Meeting Notes, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Yale College Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Yale College Hackman Retirement, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Yale College Low Income and Pell Spreadsheet, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Yale College Meeske Retirement, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Yale College Natural Science Graduates Report, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Yale College New Students Reception, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Yale College Senior Associate Dean Edwards Notes, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Yale College Standing Committee, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 87)